hello everyone this is Rahul jakara from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stop updates 3 basically
means right sector right quality and
right valuation these are our investment
ideas today we have an update on icsa
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on icsi Lombard with a price target of
rupees 1950 new wedge techn techologies
such as artificial intelligence machine
learning iot cloud and data analytics
are adding better cost efficiencies
engagement with customers improving
business sourcing and identifying early
risk alerts without incurring
substantial additional cost the business
is expected to achieve its core
objective that is agility efficiency
reliability and security over the medium
to long term we believe the company's
healthy premium market share along with
its focus on balancing growth and risk
selection using data analytics to
achieve profitable growth is the right
strategy we expect healthy premium
growth to sustain led by investment in
distribution Channel and leveraging
digital capabilities gradual Improvement
in the combined ratios should boost
profitability we expect the company to
deliver medium-term Ro of 18% at the
current market price the stock trades at
35.5 times at fi 25 and 29.8 time fi 26
earning EPS estimates the stock has
outperformed the broader esses in last
12 months next we cover Dr R's
Laboratories we interacted with the
management of the Dr re in our recent
visit to Hyderabad and we believe the
company is on track to sustain its
Superior performance both organically
and inorganically the company has
strategized its growth Vision into
Horizon 1 and Horizon 2 The Horizon 1
which includes core portfolio growth of
generics branded generics apis otcs
could not boost growth and self
strategize or 2 which have value added
products such as cdmos biologics NC nbes
digital therapetic and wellness OTC
products which would Aid growth the
company has cash of $700 million us
which to be utilized for inorganic
growth aiding in maintaining a 25% Roc
the stock is currently trading at an
attractive valuation of 16 time fi25 and
14 time fi 26 estimated EPS respectively
due to sustained growth ECT in regulated
markets such as us and Europe the
indiaan market is expected to surpass
IPM growth and higher margin trajectory
we escal a price to equity of 17 times
FY 26 EPS of R
391.35
37 investment in Securities Market are
subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing